sockdreams.com 2007-05-30

# Sock Dreams ~ Privacy Policy

## Our Privacy Policy 

We value your privacy & security. Virtual terminal has **SSL** for secure online transactions. We will NEVER sell or give your information to anyone else or add you to our mailing list simply because you’ve written or ordered.

**Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:**

  * **Our Commitment To Privacy**
  * **The Information We Collect**
  * **Our Commitment To Data Security**
  * **How To Contact Us**

### Our commitment to privacy

We respect your privacy. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

### The information we collect & how we use it:

In order to process your order we may require various forms of personal information from you depending on the payment method you choose. We will never ask for more than is necessary for the bank to verify your ability to pay with your chosen method.   
IP addresses are recorded for security purposes only in the check out process.   
If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with the user.  
We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order. 

#### Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. If you are set not to accept cookies you will not be able to add more than one item to the cart.

On some pages, you can submit feedback or leave comments and we may ask you for some additional information, you are never required to leave additional information and we will never send you unsolicited emails. The only times you will get email from us are if you ask a question, place an order or request to join our update list.

We use non-identifying and computer generated information for statistical purposes only. This includes among other things, domain, country, browser, platform & pages visited. Most websites routinely do this and we never share any of this information with anybody not directly involved with the maintenance of our website. 

### Our commitment to data security

This website takes precautions to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and off-line. When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number, driver’s license and CVV), that information is encrypted and is protected with SSL encryption software. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when you are just 'surfing'. While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also protect user-information off-line. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information.

The servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment, behind a locked door & cage.

If you have any questions about the security of our check out system, you can send an email to [CORP.EFTSECURE.SUPPORT@eftnet.com](mailto:CORP.EFTSECURE.SUPPORT@eftnet.com).

If you have any questions about the security at our website, you can send us an email. 

### How to contact us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email.
